We're here for another silicone brand. I partnered up with PumpLint and they have inflatable silicone.
How cute is that? These are paws. I can inflate them. I will inflate them. And slightly heavier.
Their feet. Also inflatable, also silicone, also pink.
I know I've already shown you several silicone brands, but this is really something new because
of the inflatable part. How does it work? You have an air pump which is basically
like your bicycle tire pump and you can inflate them. There are two layers. It's
basically glued together. We have an outside layer and an inside layer. So
it's a double layer of silicone and that's why it's also pretty heavy especially for
the shoes. The silicone is heavy by itself. Two layers of it is, you know, really
heavy. I put a slight layer of talcum on my feet and before the comments are
coming in how unhealthy talcum is I'm not eating it I'm not sleeping in it or
breathing it in I'm not doing this every day so we do a lot of unhealthy stuff in
our lives I don't think that this is going to make a difference but here we
are I'll try to get into the first foot
So I noticed that there was a bit of air inside already, I released that.
They're even squishier now.
So trying to move my toes right to the front and then just pull it carefully up like a
sock which works pretty good actually.
Done already.
Okay, now I have to pop them up.
Oh, slowly, slowly.
Wait.
Ah, there we go.
So while pumping, I noticed that the inner layer, of course, moved closer to the foot.
there's no real vacuum so my foot is not squished together still very comfy but
of course it is a bit restricting the space if there are pushes inward and here
we are we have these straps coming with the paw shoes and also some locks
They're pretty heavy.
Not that easy to lift them up.
And they're really squishy.
Really funny.
If you ever wondered if Bigfoot is real, it's now.
This feels so funny.
actually what you imagine if you think about putting a balloon around your foot
and pumping it up. Only heavier and like more high quality than a balloon. Fun!
So the colors are customizable, the pop colors. I chose pink and I do not only have the
shoes but also matching hands. So I'll try to get the hands on as well and I am
imagining at least for a second that I will need help. Same procedure I'm going
to put them inside. It's basically like a ball on the inside so round shape.
Basically like this. Oh god. It's already hard for this side.
Okay, you basically have to make a fist so your fingers won't poke the silicone too much
and you will be like very compact inside because there's not a lot of space.
I imagine even less now that I pop it up.
These are so fun! I feel like a bouncy balloon animal, I don't know. So I had the feeling that you can definitely pump them more than feet and that they're more restricting by nature and their shape.
It is pretty hard to do it by yourself for the second one and also do not
match silicone with hair because hair gets stuck to silicone
And now I can't put my hair over my face anyway
What I particularly like about it that you don't have to loop your whole body up
To get into these. It's just basically a quick fix if you want to wear some silicone and it's just so adorable
Just imagine having matching cat ears. Yeah I mean is it a cat or a dog?
I don't know what do you think? These are also not... are these dog feet? I don't know.
Or dinosaur? Bigfoot? I don't know. Anyway yeah that's fun. I was debating whether I
I should get pink or lime green or something yellow blue but yeah this is the look
now imagine having to find some socks that fit these paws
okay anyway um I need a way to figure out how to get out of them again no seriously I had help for
second hand because how would you put that on and close the buckle and everything alone
not possible but i mean your feet are fine by yourself so yeah if you have any questions leave
a comment in the comment section down below or check out all the links and discount codes i will
write in the description text check also my patreon and social media and yeah if you liked
it leave a thumbs up. I don't have thumbs anymore but you know what I mean. Yeah, hope you enjoyed
this one. I will see you in the next video. If you're interested in more silicone videos, I have
a bunch of them on my channel. I have a whole playlist so check that out. Until next time, bye!